uh what motivated me to join this
organization as a business Central
consultant is a new opportunity for me
to push myself in a growth opportunity
as being an individual in supply chain I
got firsthand experience as an end user
with Erp implementations and really just
fell in love with the process I was
looking for something that was going to
challenge me um and that would provide a
different environment for work than what
I was used to and so the idea of working
from home and being able to travel a
little bit for work was very exciting I
appreciate the talent program I'm in I
always have individuals as well as
content at my fingertips to be able to
dive in and do self-learning as well as
Collaborative Learning and it's really a
unique opportunity I am a nature lover
at heart I enjoy hiking I enjoy tattoos
I have two cats who are the light of my
life in my personal time I really enjoy
doing anything active um I like to go on
hikes I like to go repelling I like to
go mountain biking um and my favorite
activity would probably be working out I
really have enjoyed being able to go
through the the training modules in my
own time and not being thrown into
projects too early now I'm able to learn
little by little every day if you love
to learn new things every day and get
new experiences this would be the
perfect line of work onboarding with
clients first was really a Breeze I
really got to take everything at my own
pace and again be able to do learning
that was best suited for me I would
strongly suggest taking a look at a
career change to a business Central
consultant because my work life balance
has improved by
tfold